I'm so glad you're both okay.
Hey.
So, what happened?
She showed up out of nowhere...
and killed Mannen.
She said her name was Dot.
Mine called herself Hyphen.
She told me to never come back.
So... how come you didn't tell us anything?
Don't you care now you've cleared it?
Because... Because of you, Mannen—
Rika.
What would have changed?
What if you shielded Mannen?!
You would never have made it back, Rika!
You'd have been killed!
What?!
We were just worried about you!
Why didn't you contact us?
Tell us why.
No.
Huh?
I wish I'd never gotten mixed up in this mess.
Didn't you choose this?
Neiru.
It was chosen for me.
Why did you call out to me?
I'm gonna get them back for Mannen, no matter what!
Ai.
Let's leave together.
Okay.
You can't even crack your Egg like this, Ai.
They'll get you if you don't release Leon.
No.
I won't let Leon out.
If I do...
You imprinted on them as their mothers,
but we created them.
Hey, Acca...
Veni.
Leon?!
Don't hesitate now.
Break the Egg.
That is your top priority.
Huh?
You're...
me.
What's going on?
Tell me, Acca! Ura-Acca!
Are you familiar with the term "parallel world"?
Only in comic books.
They actually exist.
When someone makes an important
choice, or when they don't,
another them is created in a different, divergent space-time.
I hate to say it, but in a different
space-time, the Ai you see there...
You killed yourself, didn't you?
I'm sorry. I...
You don't have to apologize. I understand.
Because of our eyes, you were
bullied and always on your own.
I couldn't talk to Mom or anyone.
Even Koito?
Who?
I see.
I'm fighting to save my friend Koito.
Your friend?
Yeah.
I see. You made a friend.
Now I have others, too.
Neiru, Rika, Momo.
That many?
Yeah.
So, you're happy?
Super happy.
Those are Seeno Evils. They're after you.
But don't worry.
I'll protect you.
You will?
You see,
I've gotten stronger.
Strong enough to do this!
Wow.
That's amazing!
Let's run!
Okay.
Ai.
Are you okay?
What's Koito like?
She's special.
She talked to me, even though I was bullied.
Lucky.
She's your precious friend.
My friend...
I don't know anything about Koito.
Mr. Sawaki?!
That's right.
I'm your mom's fiancé.
I'm going.
Take care.
Ai,
would you help me?
All right.
Watch out!
Art is an explosion!
Follow me!
All right.
Compliance is such a pain these days!
How are we teachers supposed to blow off steam?!
Where are you aiming?
Ow, ow, ow.
This is what happens to students
who disobey their teachers.
Leon!
Thanks, Leon.
You're not Mr. Sawaki!
I am Sawaki.
I'm your first love.
Leon.
Mr. Sawaki is...
a lot nicer!
That's my public face.
People are easy to fool when you're born handsome.
What a pest!
You're a monster that my doubts and suspicions created.
The real Mr. Sawaki isn't like this.
Oh?
It sounds like my public face
has you completely fooled, too!
In that case, how about this?
Koito?
You changed your hairpin.
Yeah.
Doesn't it feel gross?
Huh?
Your shoes.
Take them off.
Sure.
Let's go.
I understand that you want to trust me.
I'm glad.
As they say, love is blind.
I knew how you felt.
You love me.
A pure, unsullied love.
Compared to adult love,
it's far more fragile, ephemeral, and beautiful.
Both you and Koito.
Adult love is dirty.
Yes, it's full of self-interest. Doesn't it make you sick?
But one day, you'll end up like that, too.
Sad, isn't it?
That's why you should die before you grow up.
Don't you agree?
A world free from care.
A comfortable world.
Won't you be happy there?
I'll support you no matter what, Ai.
You only live once. Enjoy it.
That's the same thing Kotobuki said.
Kotobuki?
Nothing.
Koito...
you regret it, right?
What?
You regret it, don't you, Ai?!
Ai?
Say it out loud!
Shout it!
I regret it.
I want to see Mom!
Now I'm really mad!
Have you forgotten what your mom did?
She got dazzled by a man and tried
to put her own desires first.
You're so shocked you don't want to admit it,
but even your mom is a stranger.
When I stopped going to school,
Mom never blamed me even once.
She was always worrying about me where
I couldn't see, so that I wouldn't know.
She said that she'd support me no matter what.
I want to support her, too.
If I don't, I'd feel bad for Mom!
You're almost pitifully innocent, Ai.
Ai?
You be happy too, Mom.
You've got my full support.
Thank you.
Ai!
I'm done with the me that craved attention.
I'm going...
to believe!
If I don't, I can't protect anyone!
Can't love anyone!
That's the same mouth you asked me out with!
Shut up!
Yes!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Koito!
Isn't that great, other me?
You can see her again soon.
I thought I wanted to hear the truth from Koito.
Maybe I don't.
You don't?
Yeah.
I think I feel grateful.
Even if she was a fake friend?
I was saved back then.
I wasn't alone anymore.
I've decided.
About what?
I'm going to become a warrior of Eros.
Huh?
I'll fight Thanatos, the temptation of death.
I don't know how to go to parallel worlds yet,
but someday, I'll bring you back.
I'm sure your mom is sad.
And I want to get strong like you.
That's silly.
I'm you, aren't I?
Yeah, I guess so.
I promise.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Ah, ah.
Ah.
Redi.
I am
Kirara Rodriguez Matured XVIII Evening Star SS Plum.
Kirara... Long name.
Huh?
What's going on?
Let me in, you bastards!
Ura-Acca.
Her mission is over.
I swear I'll bring my wallet next time!
I want to get even for Mannen!
With hatred, she'll be taken by Frill.
We'll never know unless we try.
Don't you care what happens to her?
She knows the risk.
You don't actually care about Frill, do you?
What do you mean?
As long as you can save Himari.
Come on, Ura-Acca.
Isn't that how we've always been?
I won't kill you.
I won't.
So shiny.
The other... me?
She... protected me.
Ai!
I want shiny things.
"Shiny"?
Even I...
Good luck, me.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.